<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Teteva.Com | A Place To Rest</title>
		<description>A website built just for you, which expects nothing of your time. Breathe freely, old friend. Or is it a conspiracy theory?</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 12:29:36 EDT</pubDate>
		<link>https://teteva.com/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://teteva.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<image>
			<link>https://teteva.com/</link>
			<url>https://teteva.com/meta/favicon-32x32.png</url>
			<title>Teteva.Com | A Place To Rest</title>
		</image>
        
            <item>
                <title>неділя, 23 квітня 2023 р., 18:20 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[<br />
<ins>Сума</ins> в 22,5 мільйона <mark>євро</mark> стосується <b>штрафу</b> за будівництво <strong>несанкціонованих</strong> <i>споруд</i>, а ще <br />
11 мільйонів євро – за утримання їх на місці. Іншими словами, за кожен рік, коли власники не прибирають споруди, визнані <br />
незаконними, починаючи з цього року, вони повинні будуть сплатити штраф у розмірі 11 мільйонів євро.<br />
<br />
<!-- excerpt --><br />
<br />
Власник має право подати апеляцію протягом 10 днів.<br />
На додаток до штрафу, накладеного на цей конкретний заклад, у п'ятницю був підписаний наказ про знесення несанкціонованих споруд на пляжі Псару.<br />
<br />
<br />
<img webc:is="eleventy-image" width="200, 150" alt="photo of my tabby cat" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/teteva/image/upload/v1653913421/teteva.com/artworks-jigymhh4pqrayovb-ryggyw-t3000x3000.jpg"><br />
<br />
У березні частка китайської валюти юань <mark>у глобальних платежах зросла до 2,26%. Про це повідомляє Xinhua, з посиланням на дані SWIFT</mark>.<br />
Так, юань в глобальних платежах зріс з 2,19% у лютому до 2,26% у березні. Китайська валюта за підсумками березня залишилася п’ятою валютою за активністю.<br />
Згідно з даними SWIFT минулого місяця обсяг платежів у юанях зріс на 25,04% порівняно з місяцем раніше, коли зростання становила 21,46%.<br />
Також з позиції  міжнародних платежів, за винятком єврозони, юань займає 7 місце з часткою 1,67%.<br />
#test<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-04-23T15:20:00.344Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-04-23T15:20:00.344Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>неділя, 23 квітня 2023 р., 14:21 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[<br />
Сума в 22,5 мільйона євро стосується штрафу за будівництво несанкціонованих споруд, а ще 11 мільйонів євро – за утримання їх на місці. Іншими словами, за кожен рік, коли власники не прибирають споруди, визнані незаконними, починаючи з цього року, вони повинні будуть сплатити штраф у розмірі 11 мільйонів євро.<br />
<br />
Власник має право подати апеляцію протягом 10 днів.<br />
На додаток до штрафу, накладеного на цей конкретний заклад, у п'ятницю був підписаний наказ про знесення несанкціонованих споруд на пляжі Псару.<br />
<br />
<br />
<img webc:is="eleventy-image" width="200, 150" alt="photo of my tabby cat" src="https://res.cloudinary.com/teteva/image/upload/v1653913421/teteva.com/artworks-jigymhh4pqrayovb-ryggyw-t3000x3000.jpg"><br />
<br />
У березні частка китайської валюти юань <mark>у глобальних платежах зросла до 2,26%. Про це повідомляє Xinhua, з посиланням на дані SWIFT</mark>.<br />
Так, юань в глобальних платежах зріс з 2,19% у лютому до 2,26% у березні. Китайська валюта за підсумками березня залишилася п’ятою валютою за активністю.<br />
Згідно з даними SWIFT минулого місяця обсяг платежів у юанях зріс на 25,04% порівняно з місяцем раніше, коли зростання становила 21,46%.<br />
Також з позиції  міжнародних платежів, за винятком єврозони, юань займає 7 місце з часткою 1,67%.<br />
#test<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-04-23T11:21:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-04-23T11:21:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>понеділок, 27 березня 2023 р., 10:22 за північноамериканським тихоокеанським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[<br />
Президент Бразилії Луїс Інасіо Лула да Сілва, який раніше пропонував Києву відмовитися від Криму нібито заради миру та закликав США "припинили заохочувати війну",<br />
<br />
заявив, що не прагне "комусь догодити", а <mark>намагається</mark> знайти "третю альтернативу", яка, на його думку, має повернути мир в Україні.<br />
<br />
#test<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-03-27T17:22:00.344Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-03-27T17:22:00.344Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>понеділок, 6 березня 2023 р., 09:29 за північноамериканським гірським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[it’s silly and self-defeating to pretend my peace and well-being are entirely beholden to the location i’ve put down my bags in<br />
<br />
but i spent this last week eating dinner with dear old friends, breathing deeply, and watching the sun yawn and roll itself contentedly into those mule-kicked sheets on the unmade bed of the rocky mountains <br />
<br />
and what i do know is that right now, i don’t feel like a ghost anymore.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-03-06T16:29:58.138Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-03-06T16:29:58.138Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 8 лютого 2023 р., 17:29 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i don't ever want to see your power-washing, slime-squishing, pimple-popping, domino-dropping, paint-mixing, hydraulic-pressing ✨ Content ✨ again. my attention is raw from the mechanical chafing of feeds and for-you-pages and infinite wells of engineered psychological anesthetic.<br />
<br />
i want to stand and take a deep breath at the start of the day and put down my coffee and roll up my sleeves. i want to teach my smooth and scroll-poisoned brain once more how to seek and earn satisfaction by will and dedication; the methodical pursuit of craft mastery, the meticulous untangling of narrative in a great novel, the tending vocabulary practice in a new language until it blooms into a garden of fluency.<br />
<br />
allora— andiamo.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-02-08T15:29:04.966Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-02-08T15:29:04.966Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>вівторок, 31 січня 2023 р., 05:57 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[tonight i saw a really good movie<br />
and when it was over, i started calling everyone i loved<br />
and telling them i loved them, and that i was glad to know them<br />
<br />
i’ve only ever seen my own insides through gaps torn in the skin of my palms when i crashed my bike, or the hundredth time i checked my bottom teeth in the mirror, certain they’ve gotten more crooked<br />
<br />
but i gotta be cavernous<br />
if there’s room in me enough<br />
for me to be so proud i am who i am<br />
and for me to dearly want to be someone else<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2023-01-31T03:57:27.622Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2023-01-31T03:57:27.622Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>субота, 17 грудня 2022 р., 09:00 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[through this friendship i see my own immortality. moments disintegrate into lifetimes; timelines and horizons surrender their weight freely through the shutters of an upstairs window. in every story we share, in every deep wake-the-neighbors laugh you give me, in every “listen man i really need you to be here for me tonight”. our love makes us infinite.<br />
<br />
is what you know i meant when i said<br />
<br />
ha ha ggs bro gn<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-12-17T07:00:03.987Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-12-17T07:00:03.987Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>вівторок, 29 листопада 2022 р., 20:40 за північноамериканським східним стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[the disc spins to a stop. unbeknownst to you, this is the last time the two of you will speak. the bits and bytes you two carefully arranged together: all the memories, all the Really Useful Links you swore you’d return to, all those digital tears in rain. today, something in the drive’s alignment has shifted, and stories once freely exchanged will now be held captive behind the high walls of file corruption and other spells. maybe you bumped or dropped it too many times or plugged your computer into a particularly disagreeable outlet, but whatever the case, you and the drive are no longer allies. the realm of the drive will overgrow with vines and clandestine glances and secrecy; a new country to which there will be no visitors. <br />
<br />
that is, until such a day that you encounter a new sort of sorcerer, who promises an end to The Drive’s tyranny, at a steep cost. it will be dangerous, and results will not be guaranteed, he says, but there is a chance those unfinished school projects and family photo backups will be yours once more. he will wield strange tools to alchemically blur the lines between hardware and software, working by electric lanternlight late into the evening.<br />
<br />
as dawn comes, the skin of your palms is raw with impatience, your eyes fixed forlornly on the door of the sorcerer’s workshop. after countless hours of teetering uncertainty, however, the symphonies of whirring and clicking behind the door reach their codas and fade into mechanized fermata. another lifetime passes, and the sorcerer emerges, haggard, and bearing a crisply-folded anti-static shielded pouch. his hat sits crooked upon his head and his glasses dare to slip from his nose at any moment, but after a deep exhale, his forehead pulls his face back into a warm smile. he holds the shielded bag out to you, and the chromatic gold of a new drive (a new world!) bearing all the tales and lore of its debased predecessor glints furtively from within. today is a new day, and you are a new convert. a believer in the dark art of data recovery<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-11-30T01:40:10.636Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-11-30T01:40:10.636Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>вівторок, 15 листопада 2022 р., 19:25 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[listening to new wave and photographing wyoming sunrises at treeline and downshifting into every curve in the road and smelling ponderosas and piñons and being sure you know the difference, and watching a tense cowboy standoff between the two peaks at opposing ends of the valley while they dare each other to make the first move, and looking up from the trail and breathing out into a sky that really is bigger here, somehow, and taking off your sunglasses at the sunset even though it’s still too bright because you’ve never seen colors like this before.<br />
<br />
you’re just dying to be lost in the west, again<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-11-15T17:25:34.544Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-11-15T17:25:34.544Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>пʼятниця, 11 листопада 2022 р., 07:19 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i think there was once a version of me that was so assured, he could wield his confidence and resolution like a claymore; the heart, the backbone to raise the blade and the conviction to bring it back down, but tonight i watched that young knight felled by a text message.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-11-11T05:19:17.637Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-11-11T05:19:17.637Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 31 серпня 2022 р., 21:14 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[there’s a comfort to be found on the occasion that i manage to have a bad day on the same day a friend is having theirs. it’s so easy and right just to toss my stuff into the back of the car to make room in the passenger seat; let’s talk about it, what happened, how are you feeling about that? i think it’s the same comfort one finds in paying for lunch — no no, let me get it this time, no no, i insist. of course, i’ll let you get the bill next time we go out.<br />
<br />
but truthfully it’s an honor to make this one piece into something you don’t have to think about. it feels better to hold the space to care for you than it does to take it for myself. it makes me feel like maybe i didn’t need that space at all anyway, if it was so easy to throw it in the trunk. i don’t think i‘ll ever let you pay for lunch.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-08-31T18:14:41.733Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-08-31T18:14:41.733Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>пʼятниця, 22 липня 2022 р., 07:44 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i dream often of montana — a land with a sky so big it makes it okay to feel so small; nights so quiet, your brain can’t help but to stop hollering. just look at the stars.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-07-22T04:44:14.074Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-07-22T04:44:14.074Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>пʼятниця, 15 липня 2022 р., 20:14 за північноамериканським тихоокеанським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[when it comes time for an online retreat and rendezvous, meet me in that reticent old website of ours. we’ll while cyber seconds and digital days in our private, furtive corner of the ‘Net.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-07-16T03:14:48.792Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-07-16T03:14:48.792Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>четвер, 30 червня 2022 р., 02:42 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i sometimes worry, when i choose calm nights in over late nights out, over opportunities for wild adventure, over the unknown, that i’m letting an older version of myself down. i’ve seen my future. i know my path leads ultimately back from the concrete canopies of the city into the hushed breeze, fir tree, mule deer, muted steps, evergreen forests i grew up in. i know that old man finds the kind of peace i have been desperate for since i was young, and he will hold it in his arms and carry it with him as he wearily and contentedly and dutifully ambles along his mountain trails. he will hold close that peace and contentment with a steel and quiet sureness cultivated over uncountable years of seeking it. an inured master in defending his composure.<br />
<br />
i love that old man very much. i think about him often, and while i do covet his soulful peace for myself, i aspire to make him feel as proud of me as i feel of him. i’m learning new ways to care for the body he’s loaned me, and i do my best to act with his sureness — with passion but without reaction, with logic but not without emotion.<br />
<br />
but i am still young, still temperamental and neurotic, and i am often scared of feelings or experiences when i cannot imagine how the old man would face them. i fear i have boarded many doors in case i didn’t like the solicitor behind them. i’m embarrassed of my timidness; as of yet i will give him few stories of dancing, of sex and crime, of drinking and swashbuckling and brigrandry. the stories he will recount of the time i’ve spent for him are of nights of video games and thai takeout and reading books on the subway and clicking through menus on a television. i’m not proud of this lore. it’s not what i want to give him. i couldn’t bear it if he turned back to witness the life i’ve lived for him and felt regret.<br />
<br />
it will be a balance to craft better stories for the old man without being unkind to the heart of the young one. but i will learn that balance — i will borrow his peace without hoarding it; i will feel exhilaration without terror in moments of risk and uncertainty. i will not let him be restless and resentful of his younger self for not living enough when the body was able. i will give him the serenity of having earned his quietness of soul.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-06-29T23:42:13.297Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-06-29T23:42:13.297Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 22 червня 2022 р., 00:11 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i shouldn’t be solving for all of these frictional and angular feelings, like some tired old mathematician draped over his battle-worn chalkboard. i should be in the wilds of the rocky mountain north, examining bellflowers and fireweed and potentilla and heartleaf bittercress and alpine larkspur (not to mention subalpine larkspur!) aside the trail up to some unnamed mining peak. i ought to be watching the evening sky stretch its deep blue yawn over the world, revealing the luminous astral heavens beyond our daytime and preparing next morning’s soft shimmering dew.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-06-21T21:11:57.448Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-06-21T21:11:57.448Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>понеділок, 13 червня 2022 р., 23:10 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[when was the last time you felt the kind of overwhelming, reverberative joy that quiets every frenetic thought of life beyond that moment? one which comes at no expense; one you may feel wholly and safely and freely — when was the last time you felt a joy that took days to fade?<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-06-13T20:10:12.683Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-06-13T20:10:12.683Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>неділя, 22 травня 2022 р., 00:09 за північноамериканським східним літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i’m walking along sidewalks and <br />
i’m dog ear-ing books and i’m certainly not here to make friends<br />
i’m holding hostages to tell sophomoric stories with neither plot nor punchline<br />
i’ve all the anxious insecure energy of a man raised a small town fire sign, preening and self-absorbed and superior, and<br />
i’m spending it in shops like it's a soho salary<br />
so that i may narrowly afford the chance to attend the worst parties in new york city and be<br />
a nice outfit with nothing to say<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-05-22T04:09:53.668Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-05-22T04:09:53.668Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 18 травня 2022 р., 13:16 за північноамериканським східним літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[in loving you, i don’t want you to feel (as young lovers often do) that i’m The Best Thing That’s Ever Happened To You<br />
<br />
rather, in loving you, i want to follow you around endlessly and leap over myself to open all manners of doors for you, just to be by your side through so many varied and diverse and wondrous experiences that i may witness each of countless Best Things That’ve Ever Happened To You, as they happen, time after time after time.<br />
<br />
in loving you, i want to get to watch these Best Things widen your eyes and shift your perspective and re-sort your priorities — the endless minor moments that will feel like movies, the conversations that will collapse into euphoric, delirious tears and laughter, the collated startings and endings of innumerable stories, and so many Best Things that you won’t even be able to recall them all. i want to get to watch each day change you into someone new,<br />
<br />
and, in loving you, i want to love that new someone too.<br />
]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-05-18T17:16:13.553Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-05-18T17:16:13.553Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 27 квітня 2022 р., 19:29 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[born young<br />
and raised in a small town right on the border between the Wild West and the Internet;<br />
guts and love and glory in the last two places in America<br />
where you can truly get lost.]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-04-27T16:29:36.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-04-27T16:29:36.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>субота, 23 квітня 2022 р., 08:35 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i don’t want to “hang out”, i want to know a love so calamitous & deafening that far distant poets must take cover from our ensuing avalanche; diving under desks to attempt approximate couplets, desperate to echo even a fraction of the fusillade and thunder they saw in our hearts<br />
<br />
i want to lean too far into an embrace, lose my balance and tumble endlessly with and into one another down the slope, gathering tailings as our descent accelerates to a breakneck plummet, until it’s impossible to sort through which pieces were mine or were yours when we started]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-04-23T05:35:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-04-23T05:35:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>четвер, 24 березня 2022 р., 21:24 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[some personal news: i’m moving!<br />
<br />
far, far from the intersection of Art & Technology — i’ve found a little ranch up at the end of Route 287 between the towns of Care & Consideration; there’s a little diner where you can sit and drink coffee from an off-white victor mug that never empties.<br />
<br />
you can while the day there, meeting quiet neighbors and kind, chatty strangers; drifters all, who don’t ever need anyone else’s time, but are happy when it might be spared. you can listen if you want — watch threads loomed into illustrative anthologies that may be donned year-round, and will always fit as if meticulously tailored; you’ll never need to say a word.<br />
<br />
here, patience grows untended among bright Wyoming wildflowers — it makes the morning air feel crisp in your lungs. the streams this time of year are just beginning to shake ice free and mutter to themselves, and you may see the water is well-stocked with wild, untamed composure and equanimity.]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-03-24T19:24:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-03-24T19:24:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>пʼятниця, 18 лютого 2022 р., 17:40 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i don’t think i want “equity in the form of vesting options and a clear path to promotion”, i want a well-organized kitchen with open cabinets, so when the sunlight pours in through the large bifold window over the sink, it shatters into millions of prismatic shards on each glass<br />
<br />
i want to let in the morning early spring sun & its crisp breeze chaperone to glance across neatly stacked white ceramic plates and mugs, like a kind older couple at a gallery opening, and i want to watch a curious parcel of mule deer flirt between the forest and nearby clearing<br />
<br />
if by “open to new opportunities”, you mean the infinite number of warm new days and quiet frontiers hiding in every golden plain and conversational creek in the rocky mountain west; if you mean never choosing same-day shipping or nervous meetings or unkind car horns, then yes,<br />
<br />
i don’t mind if after all of this, my life amounts to anything by the yardstick of capital; if i don’t quite make it into the photo finish of the rat race. i think if at the end of this, all i’ve done is opened the door for strangers and lost count of sunrises, that’d be okay.]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-02-18T15:40:20.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-02-18T15:40:20.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>вівторок, 25 січня 2022 р., 19:45 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[instead of redesigning your portfolio<br />
try carefully folding it into the shape of a sailboat, letting it drift off down the creek, and enjoying the rest of your walk through the wild woods, unafflicted. <br />
<br />
breathe deeply from your lungs,<br />
perhaps for the first time<br />
in a long time.]]></description>
                <pubDate>2022-01-25T17:45:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2022-01-25T17:45:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>середа, 10 листопада 2021 р., 17:04 за східноєвропейським стандартним часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i don’t want to “carve out a few minutes to connect about this role”, i want to carve out a little plot of land in the wild western united states and watch the sun rise over the rockies and watch the steam from my coffee drift up to intermingle with the cool mists of the morning<br />
<br />
i want to sleep in a subalpine field among the elephantella and the limber pine and the wildflowers, running out of numbers to count the stars with,<br />
<br />
no sound but the wind and your heartbeat]]></description>
                <pubDate>2021-11-10T15:04:04.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2021-11-10T15:04:04.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>субота, 16 жовтня 2021 р., 14:39 за північноамериканським гірським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i find myself once again at the gate of the rocky mountains, the bold defenders of the western coast. the golden gaze of the sun lights the path from these quiet plains to the patient and sacred evergreen woods.<br />
<br />
in the words of our poet cy warman,<br />
<br />
“i just feel good all over.”]]></description>
                <pubDate>2021-10-16T20:39:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2021-10-16T20:39:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>четвер, 7 жовтня 2021 р., 18:55 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[<br />
why concern yourself with "developer experience" when you ought to be concerned with "the human experience"? what is autocompletion in the face of the exquisite, spectral agony of realizing you’re falling out of love? what is a “build time” under the glare of impending, relentless mortality?<br />
<br />
one day, you will die, and your legacy will be washed away when someone forgets to renew the DNS.]]></description>
                <pubDate>2021-10-07T15:55:00.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2021-10-07T15:55:00.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title>неділя, 25 квітня 2021 р., 07:18 за східноєвропейським літнім часом</title>
                <description><![CDATA[i’m on the search for a monumental, destructive, tectonic, soul-awakening, heart-shattering, immense, immersive, inundating, once-in-100-lifetimes kind of love and for some reason i have decided i will find it on a mobile phone app]]></description>
                <pubDate>2021-04-25T04:18:43.000Z</pubDate>
                <guid isPermaLink="false">2021-04-25T04:18:43.000Z</guid>
            </item>
        
	</channel>
</rss>